Hello friends, you are very welcome.
Friends, today in this video we will talk about the
roles and responsibilities of a business unit manager or
what tasks a business unit manager
performs in any organization. Hello
friends, you are very welcome. Friends,
my name is Vinod and you are watching my
YouTube channel whose name is Vinod Singh
Thakur. Friends, if you have
not subscribed to my YouTube channel, then please
subscribe to my channel so that you can
get notifications of new videos related to my job.
Without any delay, let us try to know what are the
roles and responsibilities of a business unit manager.
Friends, to run any organization,
policies and seniority are required.
No business can exist without any policy and procedure.
So friends, the work of this business unit manager is to
incorporate the policies and procedures in the business to run the operations of any business unit or to
make policies and procedures for the operation of any business unit so that the business
unit can run well. Friends, now
in school, in business  The most important job of a business unit manager is to monitor project activities
and
try to complete the project within a given time and budget.
Friends, this is the
job of a business unit manager. Keeping in mind the
strategic growth or natural
activity of any organization, the business unit manager matches all the
activities of the business unit to them, that is, the nature of
any business
unit
depends on the organization. So, the
job of a business unit manager is to first of all focus
on the descendants of the organization
and focus on how it can be done. It is the
job of a business unit manager to manage the marketing
activities. The most important job of a business unit manager is to
manage, review or oversee the
marketing activities. The marketing
department is directly
related to the subscription. If the marketing
of any product is being done well, then the
products of the business should be maintained.
Friends, if we talk about any business unit
manager, then the responsibility of a business unit
manager is that
He can increase his subscriber potential customers
strong relationship subscription
and now
profit can be earned for school and questions
Friends, if we talk about a business unit manager, then
a business unit manager should have strong
management skills in business.
In business, the unit manager can manage his management
very easily in the startup appointed by him. The
most work of a subscriber manager is to
validate the system and work in the subscriber team.
If there is a vacancy, then he should
motivate that member so that they can perform well
and the appointment can be made and
hello friends, the work of a business unit manager is that
he develops a
harmonious environment in his organization or in his team,
it creates so that at
one time the
feeling of team spirit develops which is
very beneficial for the organization.
Friends, the most important job responsibilities of a business unit manager are that
he informs the market friends
if there is any opportunity
in the market.  So a business unit manager
tries to graph it and
convert that new opportunity into something
that can generate profit for the business
or develop sales
or whatever you want to accomplish with Google.
Friends, a business unit
manager coordinates with the marketing team
and
together with the marketing team, plans the operational plan for any new
product launch. The
marketing
and business event manager's job is to integrate that planning. What strategy will be there for
a product to be launched in the market,
what will be the
policy, should be
employed so that
our new product can be
launched successfully. So, the
most important job of this business unit manager is
that he
coordinates with the marketing team in creating an
operational plan for the launch of a new product. On the
other hand, the unit manager
works as a senior manager. He
works under the supervision of
a business.  The
job of a unit manager is to do those tasks,
so if you like this
video then
subscribe to my channel, like and comment, that's all for
now, thank you.